https://www.azpm.org/privacy/

AZPM Summer Adventure Club
Congratulations Graduates!
Donate
AZPM Privacy PolicyThis privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their 'Personally Identifiable Information' (PII) is being used online. PII, as described in US privacy law and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our website?When donating or contacting us through our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, email address, mailing address, phone number or other details to help you with your experience.Non-identifiable information such as cookie and usage data may be collected through Google Analytics to help track and examine the use of AZPM.org, prepare reports on activities and share them with other Google services. Google may use the data collected to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network.
When do we collect personal information?We collect personal information from you when you subscribe to a newsletter, donate to us, or enter information on our site. How do we use your information?We may use the information we collect from you when you register, make a donation, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, browse the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:To personalize your experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content offerings in which you are most interested.To send periodic emails regarding your membership or our programming, events, and services.To follow up with you after correspondence (social media, email, or phone inquiries)Arizona Public Media does not sell or exchange its mailing list with any commercial entity. We may, however, occasionally trade our list with other non-profit organizations solely for membership purposes. If you do not wish your name to be included on our trade list, please let our membership office know. We will withhold your name from the list exchange.How do we protect your information?Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. In addition, all sensitive/credit information you supply is encrypted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology.We implement a variety of security measures when a user enters, submits, or accesses their information to maintain the safety of your personal information.All transactions are processed through a gateway provider and are not stored or processed on our servers.Do we use 'cookies'?We use Google Analytics to collect data about our traffic via Google advertising cookies and identifiers, in addition to data collected through a standard Google Analytics implementation. Occasionally by visiting our site, third parties may place cookies on your browser for targeted advertising purposes. These cookies contain information on website activity, IP address, and cookie identifiers. This data may be used to target advertising on other sites based on your online activity.You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser settings. Since each browser is a little different, look at your browser's Help Menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.If you turn cookies off, some of the features that make your site experience more efficient may not function properly.Opting out of third-part trackingOur users can opt out of third-party tracking at any time. To opt out, please visit the DAA opt-out site here or the Google Analytics opt-out site here.Third-party disclosureWe do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your Personally Identifiable Information.Third-party linksOccasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third-party products or services on our website. These third-party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.California Online Privacy Protection ActCalOPPA is the first state law in the nation to require commercial websites and online services to post a privacy policy. The law's reach stretches well beyond California to require any person or company in the United States (and conceivably the world) that operates websites collecting Personally Identifiable Information from California consumers to post a conspicuous privacy policy on its website stating exactly the information being collected and those individuals or companies with whom it is being shared. - See more hereAccording to CalOPPA, we agree to the following:Users can visit our site anonymously.Once this privacy policy is created, we will add a link to it on our home page or as a minimum, on the first significant page after entering our website.Our Privacy Policy link includes the word 'Privacy' and can easily be found on the page specified above.You will be notified of any Privacy Policy changes on our Privacy Policy page.You can change your personal information by emailing or calling us.How does our site handle Do Not Track signals?We honor Do Not Track signals and Do Not Track, plant cookies, or use advertising when a Do Not Track (DNT) browser mechanism is in place.Fair Information PracticesThe Fair Information Practices Principles form the backbone of privacy law in the United States and the concepts they include have played a significant role in the development of data protection laws around the globe. Understanding the Fair Information Practice Principles and how they should be implemented is critical to comply with the various privacy laws that protect personal information.In order to be in line with Fair Information Practices we will take the following responsive action, should a data breach occur we will notify you via email within 7 business days.Email address collectionWe collect your email address in order to send information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions. We also may use it to market to our mailing list if you have subscribed to receive such emails.If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can follow the instructions at the bottom of each email and we will promptly remove you from such correspondence.Contacting usIf there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, you may contact us using the information below.Arizona Public Media
The University of Arizona Modern Languages Building, Room 223
1423 E. University Blvd.
Tucson, AZ 85719Contact Us via Email
CONNECT
Newsletter
Facebook
Twitter
News Twitter
Instagram
YouTube
Privacy Policy
Arizona Public Media broadcast stations are licensed to the Arizona Board of Regents. Arizona Public Media and AZPM are registered trademarks of the Arizona Board of Regents.
